   <legalnotice id="legalnotice">
         <para
>Tätä asiakirjaa saa kopioida, jakaa edelleen ja/tai muokata Free Software Foundationin julkaiseman GNU Free Documentation Licensen (GFDL) version 1.1 tai valinnaisesti myöhemmän version mukaisesti, ilman vaatimuksia muuttamattomista osioista ja etu- tai takakansiteksteistä. Kopion GFDL:stä voi nähdä napsauttamalla <ulink type="help" url="ghelp:fdl"
>tätä linkkiä</ulink
>, tai lukemalla ohjeen mukana toimitetun COPYING-DOCS-nimisen tiedoston. </para>
          <para
>Tämä käyttöohje on osa Gnomen käyttöohjekokoelmaa, jota levitetään GFDL-lisenssin alaisena. Jos haluat levittää tätä käyttöohjetta erillään kokoelmasta, voit tehdä sen liittämällä lisenssin kopion ohjeen mukaan, kuten lisenssin luku 6 sanelee. </para>
 
         <para
>Monet nimistä, joita yhtiöt käyttävät tuotteistansa ja palveluistansa, ovat tuotemerkkejä. Gnomen dokumentointiprojektissa nämä nimet pyritään kirjoittamaan suuraakkosin tai isolla alkukirjaimella, sikäli kun projektin jäsenet tietävät kyseisistä tuotemerkeistä. </para>
 
         <para
>DOCUMENT AND MODIFIED VERSIONS OF THE DOCUMENT ARE PROVIDED UNDER THE TERMS OF THE GNU FREE DOCUMENTATION LICENSE WITH THE FURTHER UNDERSTANDING THAT: <orderedlist>
                 <listitem>
                   <para
>DOCUMENT IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, WARRANTIES THAT THE DOCUMENT OR MODIFIED VERSION OF THE DOCUMENT IS FREE OF DEFECTS MERCHANTABLE, FIT FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGING. THE ENTIRE RISK AS TO THE QUALITY, ACCURACY, AND PERFORMANCE OF THE DOCUMENT OR MODIFIED VERSION OF THE DOCUMENT IS WITH YOU. SHOULD ANY DOCUMENT OR MODIFIED VERSION PROVE DEFECTIVE IN ANY RESPECT, YOU (NOT THE INITIAL WRITER, AUTHOR OR ANY CONTRIBUTOR) ASSUME THE COST OF ANY NECESSARY SERVICING, REPAIR OR CORRECTION. THIS DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY CONSTITUTES AN ESSENTIAL PART OF THIS LICENSE. NO USE OF ANY DOCUMENT OR MODIFIED VERSION OF THE DOCUMENT IS AUTHORIZED HEREUNDER EXCEPT UNDER THIS DISCLAIMER; AND </para>
                 </listitem>
                 <listitem>
                   <para
>UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES AND UNDER NO LEGAL THEORY, WHETHER IN TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), CONTRACT, OR OTHERWISE, SHALL THE AUTHOR, INITIAL WRITER, ANY CONTRIBUTOR, OR ANY DISTRIBUTOR OF THE DOCUMENT OR MODIFIED VERSION OF THE DOCUMENT, OR ANY SUPPLIER OF ANY OF SUCH PARTIES, BE LIABLE TO ANY PERSON FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OF ANY CHARACTER INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF GOODWILL, WORK STOPPAGE, COMPUTER FAILURE OR MALFUNCTION, OR ANY AND ALL OTHER DAMAGES OR LOSSES ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO USE OF THE DOCUMENT AND MODIFIED VERSIONS OF THE DOCUMENT, EVEN IF SUCH PARTY SHALL HAVE BEEN INFORMED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. </para>
                 </listitem>
           </orderedlist>
         </para>
   </legalnotice>
 
